<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Graffiti Grid]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Graffiti Grid]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/graffiti-grid/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 09:59:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/graffiti-grid/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SWISS ARMY MAN (2016) MOVIE REVIEW: HOME IS WHERE THE FARTING CORPSE IS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Swiss Army Man‘s reputation precedes itself. When you reanimate the corpse of our cinematicHarry Potter, Daniel Radcliffe, and have his arsehole barking out more noises than the guy from Police Academy,you’d expect the attention. Add a few choice adverts with Paul Dano’s bearded castaway Hank joyously riding Radcliffe’s corpse Manny as a flatulence powered jet-ski and you’ve got something that’s too tantalising to miss. If you can look (and listen) past your beloved “boy who lived” corpse squirting sphincter morse code to Hank you have an exceptional debut from two exciting young filmmakers: Dan Kwan and Daniel Scheinert (The Daniels). It’s really not since Spike Jonze’s Her that I’ve seen a film that so profoundly gets loneliness, longing and love.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/graffiti-grid/swiss-army-man-2016-movie-review-home-is-where-the-fartin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7dc65133-67b4-4374-a37f-44b43433427b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 09:59:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/df497039-6726-4dd6-ace1-a07e4366cb34.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/graffiti-grid/bf694188-6c6f-4f88-8b9b-6dbe02ac1e23/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bf694188-6c6f-4f88-8b9b-6dbe02ac1e23</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 20:42:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE REVENANT (ALEJANDRO GONZÁLEZ IÑÁRRITU – 2015) MOVIE REVIEW]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE REVENANT (ALEJANDRO GONZÁLEZ IÑÁRRITU – 2015) MOVIE REVIEW</h1><p>When a fur trapping expedition is ambushed by a native tribe on a murderous pursuit to find their Chief’s kidnapped daughter, guide Hugh Glass (Leonardo DiCaprio) and his son Hawk (Forrest Goodluck) must lead the survivors, Andrew Henry (Domhnall Gleeson), Jim Bridger (Will Poulter), John Fitzgerald (Tom Hardy) and others through the unforgiving wilderness back to their fort. After a grizzly bear attack at the beginning of their journey Glass is left clinging to the threads of life. Henry (Glesson) makes the tough decision to leave Hawk, Bridger and Fitzgerald behind to attend to Glass and lead the rest of the crew home. When Fitzgerald’s greed gets the better of his patience, he murders Hawk, half buries Glass alive and forces Bridger into becoming a false witness to the events. Fuelled by profound vengeance Glass wills his body to overcome a pitiless natural world and unforgiving natives while still in pursuit to find the man who to extinguished his reason to live.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f19709b0950a311f21ad1801efc3030ad181e34e.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/graffiti-grid/the-revenant-alejandro-gonzalez-inarritu-2015-movie-revi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e02c4dd2-6e4c-4b72-8a72-e2d537d8f863</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 20:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>